

## Profile

I am a Software/Front-end Developer in PT Inovasi Otomasi Teknologi with over 2 years of experience and aspiring to be a Frontend Developer and Fullstack developer in the future. Throughout my university experience, from making my first PyGame, making MySQL databases, creating recognition systems, to building web applications, and nothing makes me happier than seeing the program runs without any errors. I am looking forward to further enhance my skills and also my career in the computer science field.

## Employment History

## Software/Front-end Developer at PT Inovasi Otomasi Teknologi, Jakarta

July 2023

- Tasked with creating customized dashboards for users ranging from paperless e-forms to monitoring dashboard
- Mostly used React.js for front-end development, Laravel for back-end development, and MySQL for the database.
- Experienced in creating custom OEE (Overall Equipment Effectiveness) dashboards
- Deployed applications in Linux, Docker, and AWS environments.

## Business Analyst at PT Amber Solusi Internasional, Jakarta

September 2022 — February 2023

- Worked as a contractor to be outsourced to PT Zurich Asuransi Indonesia in the IT Application Delivery Division.
- Provide data and reporting to users using Microsoft SQL Server and Microsoft Excel.

## Front-end Developer at Ninety Seven Web Developer, Jakarta

April 2021 — August 2021

- Develop the front-end for website or desktop apps.
- Working with ReactJS and MongoDB for API.
- Implementing API requests for the product.

#### Education

# Bachelor of Computer Science, Binus University International, Jakarta

September 2018 — July 2022

Graduated with 3.67 GPA, I completed all the courses that the Faculty of Computer Science has to offer in Binus University International.

#### High School Diploma, Sekolah Victory Plus, Bekasi

August 2016 — May 2018

Graduated with a 3.5 GPA in Natural Sciences major.

#### **Details**

Jln. Vernonia Barat 1, Blok DB/07, Cluster Vernonia, Summarecon Bekasi Bekasi, 17143 Indonesia +6281324775830 sianandarjason@gmail.com

#### Date / Place of birth

15 November 2000 Jakarta

Nationality

Indonesian

**Driving license** 

A and C

Links

LinkedIn Github

**Skills** 

Docker

SQL

MongoDB

React

Node.js

**Bootstrap** 

Git

Python

MySQL

jQuery

**CSS** 

HTML5

PHP

JavaScript

Express.js

### Courses

## The Web Developer Bootcamp 2022, Udemy

August 2021 — November 2021

MERN Stack Front To Back: Full Stack React, Redux, & Node.js, Udemy

November 2021 — December 2021

## Internships

## Front End Engineer Specialist at Sagara Technology, Jakarta

August 2021 — February 2022

- Responsible for translating UI/UX Designs to be a responsive web app.
- Responsible for creating pages for the product's landing page and dashboard.
- Responsible for implementing API requests for the product.
- Tech used:
  - React JS
  - Next JS
  - SCSS

## Mobile Application Developer at NHS, Jakarta

February 2021 — May 2021

- Developed and implemented mobile app prototype based on client requirements.
- Understand about the healthcare system.
- Using Dart language and Flutter Framework supported with Android Studio.

#### **Hobbies**

Basketball, Video Games, Drawing

## Languages

Indonesia

English